Cameron Rutherford

Resume

Summary

High Performance Computing Research Software Engineer with over 3 years of experience deploying, testing and optimizing scientific software and systems.

Skills

LanguagesDevelopment ToolsFrameworksPythonGit, pre-commitQuarto / nbdevC, C++VSCode / JupyterLabDistributed ML / Parallel ComputingLinux, bashGitHub / GitLab pipelinesPytorch, LLAMA, AWSQiskit, QASM, Q#Docker, Conda, Spack, Poetry
Quarto, Sphinx, LaTeX

Experience

Software Engineer HPC/ML/Q, Pacific Northwest National Laboratory (Virtual) 2020 - Present

- test
- test
- test

Sports Events Coordinator, Whitworth University (Spokane, WA)

2019-2020

- test
- test
- test

IT Intern, Keysight Technologies (Colorado Springs, CO)

Summer 2018

- test
- test
- test

Education

Bachelor of Mathematics and Computer Science

May 2020

Whitworth University, Summa Cum Laude, Outstanding Mathematician

Extra

Whitworth Chess Club President	2019-2020
Whitworth Men's Basketball Team	2016-2019